<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Color Picker</string>
    <string name="red_initial_val">R: 0</string>
    <string name="green_initial_val">G: 0</string>
    <string name="blue_initial_val">B: 0</string>
    <string name="hex_value">Hex: #000000</string>
    <string name="hur_initial_val">H: 0°</string>
    <string name="sat_initial_val">S: 0%</string>
    <string name="val_initial_val">V: 0%</string>
    <string name="random_text">Random</string>

    <string name="overview_text">
        Color Picker:\n
        Primary colors are any of a group of colors from
        which all other colors can be obtained by mixing.
        In real world applications the most common colors
        chosen are red, blue, and yellow. When it come to
        representing colors digitally, the RGB24 (red, green,
        blue) model is most popular.
        This App lets you play around with different model and lets
        you generate your own colors.
    </string>
    <string name="howToUse_text">
        How to Use:\n
        RGB and HSV:\n
        Move the slider to select a value from 0-255
        (0-360 for hue, 0-100 for saturation and value).
        Do this for each slider to get your desired color.\n
        Hex:\n
        Enter a valid hexadecimal color value (i.e. 0-9, A-F)
        and hit enter on your keyboard.\n
        When a desired color is found you can copy the
        hexadecimal value to your clipboard via the \"Save\"
        option. This will also save the
        color in your \"Saved Colors\" menu.\n
        Saved Colors:\n
        To resave the hexadecimal value to your clipboard,
        tap the desired color from your list of colors. If you
        wish to delete a color from your Saved Colors menu,
        press and hold.
    </string>
    <string name="rgb_about_text">
        (RGB)\n
        This scheme restricts the
        number of available values to 8 bits in three color
        channels with values of 0–255. This means that any
        given color can be one of 16,777,216 possible colors.
    </string>
    <string name="hsv_about_text">
        (HSV)\n
        Hue, Saturation, Value is an alternative representations
        of the RGB color model. It more closely aligns with the
        way human vision perceives color-making attributes.
        The HSV representation models the way paints of different
        colors mix together, with the saturation dimension resembling
        various shades of brightly colored paint, and the value
        dimension resembling the mixture of those paints with
        varying amounts of black or white paint.
    </string>
    <string name="cymk_about_text">
        (CMYK)\n
        Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, Black is a subtractive color model,
        used in color printing. The CMYK model works by partially or
        entirely masking colors on a lighter, usually white, background.
        The ink reduces the light that would otherwise be reflected.
    </string>
    <string name="hex_about_text">
        (Hex)\n
        A hex triplet is a six-digit, three-byte hexadecimal number used
        to represent colors in computing applications. The bytes
        represent the red, green and blue components of the color.
        One byte represents a number in the range 00 to FF (in hexadecimal
        notation), or 0 to 255 in decimal notation.
    </string>

</resources>
